(Girl:)I'll take your word for it.
(Howard:)You should.
(Howard:)He's really looked.
(Raj:)I'm Raj, by the way.
(Raj:)This is Howard.
Hi.
(Girl:)Claire.
Well, I've seen you here before,
Claire.
(Claire:)It's my first time.
(Claire:)I'm looking for inspiration
for this movie I'm writing.
(Howard:)You're a screenwriter?
(Claire:)Well, screenwriter,
slash bartender,
(Claire:)slash, a month away
from living in my car.
(Raj:)Yeah, I get that.
(Raj:)I'm a scientist,
(Raj:)slash party planner,
(Raj:)slash small-dog enthusiast,
(Claire:)slash...
(Raj:)guy who probably should have
stopped at “scientist.”
(Claire:)You're really a scientist?
(Raj:)Well, astrophysicist.
(Claire:)That's perfect.
(Claire:)Do you think I could pick your
brain for my movie some time?
(Claire:)It's animated sci-fi for kids.
(Raj:)Sure. I love animated movies.
He does,
and he has the Lilo & Stitch
collector plates to prove it.
(Raj:)Excuse me for wanting
a little magic in my life.
(Claire:)Here's my number.